const list = [
  {
    question: "An HTML document can contain _____",
    options: ["Attributes", "Tags", "Raw text", "All the answers are true"],
    answer: "All the answers are true",
  },
  {
    question: "A page designed in HTML is called _____",
    options: ["Application", "Cover page", "Front-end", "Web Page"],
    answer: "Web Page",
  },
  {
    question: "The HTML document contains a root tag called ____",
    options: ["HEAD", "Title", "Body", "HTML"],
    answer: "HTML",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If we want to place text around an image, which CSS property should we use?",
    options: ["push", "float", "align", "wrap"],
    answer: "float",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Can we align an element by setting margin-left and margin-right?",
    options: ["Yes its possible.", "No, its not possible."],
    answer: "No, its not possible.",
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the correct HTML tag for a large title.",
    options: ["H1", "Heading", "Head", "H6"],
    answer: "H1",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If we want to use a nice green dotted border around an image, which css property are we going to use?",
    options: [
      "border-line",
      "border-style",
      "border-decoration",
      "border-color",
    ],
    answer: "border-style",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
    options: ["var", "let", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
    answer: "Both A and B",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript?",
    options: [
      "getElementById()",
      "getElementByClassName()",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    answer: "Both A and B",
  },
  {
    question: "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
    options: ["const", "var", "let", "constant"],
    answer: "const",
  },
];
export default list;
